<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<stories>
  
  <story>
    <id>1652501937</id>
    <title>WinterHaven</title>
    <author>Leroy B. Vaughn</author>
    <date>May/14/2022</date>
    <content>Doesn’t this woman ever shut up, Peter Scoggins asked himself as his wife yapped non stop for over three hours. She started before they got into the car at their home in Long Beach, California. This was Peter’s second wife. He had been married to a Korean woman that he met overseas in the Army for forty years before she died of cancer.&#13;
One of his friends at the chemical plant that he retired from had introduced him to his current wife and he had regretted marrying her after about three days. Now I know why she’s been married six times he told himself as she went on and on.&#13;
Peter looked at the highway sign that indicated that Yuma was fifty miles ahead. That meant that they had less than forty five miles to go. They were headed to a little Mexican town named Los Algodones, known locally as molar city. One of his wife’s girlfriends had recommended a dentist in Los Algodones and his wife needed a lot of dental work.&#13;
Tijuana and Mexicali were both closer to Long Beach, but other people had told her that Los Algodones was much easier to get around in. It was a small town filled with dental offices, opticians, pharmacies and liquor stores. Things that American senior citizens needed at low costs.&#13;
His wife made reservations at an Indian casino and hotel about two miles north of Los Algodones and nine miles west of Yuma, Arizona. They spent the rest of the afternoon and part of that evening in the casino. His wife was disappointed that there was no bingo parlor, but she found several slot machines that she liked.&#13;
Peter slipped out of the side door to take a look around the desert. It had been almost fifty years since he had been to Los Algodones. His wife had no idea that he had ever been there before. He didn’t recognize anything but he was fairly sure that grandpa must have parked the old trailer near the spot where the casino now stood.&#13;
xxxxxxxxxx&#13;
It was the winter of 1970. Tommy and Peter worked at a chemical plant in Long Beach, California and Tommy had invited Peter to spend the weekend out in the desert with his grandpa. Grandpa had an old travel trailer that he would be sleeping in and the boys were planning on sleeping in sleeping bags.&#13;
After a little over four hours grandpa turned off the highway. They were almost in Yuma, Arizona and the boys were tired of being on the road.&#13;
They thought they were going to freeze their asses off that first night. Neither one of the boys knew how cold the desert got at night in February. Grandpa told them that he slept well and they were just soft when they both complained about freezing. “You boys will be okay. We’ll make a run across the border tonight and pick up some blackberry brandy,” the old man informed them.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
The Mexican border was about two miles south of their campsite, and grandpa told them they would have to be back at the border crossing before ten that night. The U. S. border at Los Algodones closed every night at ten and opened again at six in the morning.&#13;
Grandpa took them to his favorite cantina and they were greeted by six prostitutes and a bartender. It was a slow night and they were the only customers in the cantina. Grandpa saw the two nineteen-year old’s eyeballing the scantily clad hookers and said, “If you boys want to get a little poontang go ahead. I’ll be drinking beer right here at the bar.”&#13;
The boys had both hoped that the trip would be good and so far they were off to a good start, judging by the dark skinned women trying to get their attention at the bar. Tommy selected the tall dark haired one with the see-through blouse showing large breasts with big round nipples popping out against the material.&#13;
The youngest hooker, maybe a year or two older than Peter didn’t say anything, she just looked at Peter with her light green eyes and reached out and took his hand leading him to her crib in the back of the cantina.&#13;
After they were finished, Peter handed her a ten-dollar bill and she gave it back to him. She had not said one word the entire time and he was surprised when she told him in English. “Keep your money, I like you.” Peter told her he liked her also and he was coming back soon to see her again.&#13;
Tommy was waiting for him at the bar. Both of the boys had big smiles on their faces and grandpa looked at them and said, “Must have been some good stuff. I’m too old to cut the mustard but I can still lick the jar.”&#13;
They left for the liquor store and grandpa told them to get two bottles each of blackberry brandy, that was the limit for Americans at U.S. customs.&#13;
They crossed back over into California and grandpa drank his brandy while he sang with his five rag-tag Chihuahua’s. The boys drank beer and looked at the stars. Peter never mentioned the young hooker giving him his money back. He figured that no one would believe him.&#13;
xxxxxxxxxx&#13;
Peter came back to the border alone three more times. He stayed with Blanca for an entire day and night each time giving her enough money to make up for her lost customers. Peter was planning on moving to Yuma, Arizona to be close to her, and then he got his draft notice. He visited her one more time when he told her he was going into the Army. Blanca often thought about him as the years went by, but never saw him again. &#13;
xxxxxxxxxx&#13;
They were in the parking lot across from the border checkpoint at eight the next morning. His wife’s appointment was at nine, but they didn’t know that it would only take them five minutes to go from the checkpoint to the dental office.&#13;
They walked from the parking lot into a tunnel made of chain link wire to the Mexican side of  the border. Americans and Canadians were already flocking to the Mexican side and the Mexican customs officers were waving everybody in. &#13;
They were greeted by a Mexican man whose job was to steer patients to the dentist that employed him, but he was nice enough to direct them to the dentist that Peter’s wife selected. His office was a two minute walk from the border.&#13;
They were forty five minutes early but the receptionist told them that the doctor could see her now.  Peter’s wife was surprised and told the receptionist so. The receptionist said, “In Mexico the doctor works for you.” &#13;
“Wow” Peter exclaimed as the receptionist led his wife into the room where the work would be done. When she returned, the receptionist explained that the doctor had done a complete exam and his wife would need several procedures. She would be put to sleep using gas and with the procedure and the gas she would need at least two hours to recover.&#13;
Peter decided to take a look around the town after he gave the receptionist his cell phone number in case something happened. The cantina that he and Tommy had gone to years ago was now an eye doctor’s office as far as Peter could tell. It was on a corner two blocks south of the dental office he had just left. He walked down the block passing several tiny stalls and curio shops selling the usual t-shirts, baseball caps, belts, trinkets and souvenirs of Mexico. Almost all are made in China or Taiwan.&#13;
He walked past an older woman wearing a cotton dress with an apron. She was selling homemade tamales, according to her sign written in English. He didn’t know why but he turned around and approached the tamale woman. He looked at her tamales for a few seconds before he looked up and saw her staring at him.&#13;
He looked directly into her light green eyes as she looked back into his and said, “I didn’t think you would ever come back Peter.”&#13;
“I can’t believe it’s you Blanca, after all these years.”&#13;
They stood in the same spot for over one hour and talked. He told her all about his life, his Korean wife, his time overseas in the Army and his new wife that was having dental work done. Peter asked if he could come back in the afternoon and talk some more. They agreed to meet at four that afternoon in the same place. Peter told her he was going to take her to dinner and she said she would wear something nicer than her old cotton dress.&#13;
After they got back to the hotel, Peter's wife just wanted to sleep. The dentist had prescribed Percocet and she would be out for several hours. She slept until three in the afternoon and wondered where Peter had gone. &#13;
She didn’t need him for anything and she assumed that he was down in the casino drinking at the bar. His cell phone was turned off and she knew that he didn’t want to be bothered. She took a shower and headed for the casino.&#13;
Peter got back to the border checkpoint fifteen minutes before the gate closed for the night. He didn’t have anything to declare and he told the customs agent that he had been in Mexico to have dinner with an old friend. &#13;
His wife came to the room and didn’t bother to ask where he had been. Peter suggested that she take another Percocet before going to bed and she agreed that would be a good idea.&#13;
She was sound asleep when Peter woke up at fifteen minutes after five the next morning. He was glad that they had packed separate bags for the trip as he picked up his backpack and slipped out the door.&#13;
His wife was still a little groggy when she woke up at nine that morning. She wanted to head back to Long Beach but Peter did not answer when she called his name. She checked the bathroom and assumed that he was downstairs in the casino until she noticed his cell phone, car keys and hotel room key on the nightstand next to where he had slept. She looked out the window and saw their car parked in the same spot they had parked in when they came back from Los Algodones.&#13;
She went downstairs and asked the desk clerk to page Peter Scoggins. After fifteen minutes she asked the desk clerk to call the local law enforcement agency. She was waiting in the hotel lobby when the deputy sheriff arrived. She wanted to report a missing person.&#13;
He asked several questions and she told him they had been married for about three years and why they were at the hotel. They had separate bedrooms and lived in an apartment building. They had separate bank accounts and he was not senile.&#13;
Based on this the deputy would not file a missing person’s report, or send out a silver alert for a missing senior citizen. He thought there were two possibilities. One he may have found a ride and left her, or two he may have walked into Mexico. &#13;
The deputy called U.S. customs at the border and they verified that Peter Scoggins had been in Mexico twice yesterday. They had no idea if he returned to Mexico that day. They only recorded people coming from Mexico not going into Mexico. &#13;
That afternoon Scoggins' wife headed back to Long Beach wondering how she would find husband number seven.&#13;
</content>
  </story>
  <story>
    <id>1652502056</id>
    <title>3:33 AM</title>
    <author>Alexander James</author>
    <date>May/14/2022</date>
    <content>Ever since they moved into her grandmother’s old house way on top of Bannockburn Hill, he had woken up every morning at 3:33 A.M. without fail.&#13;
He hated the old house. He hated the way it creaked and moaned. The way it seem to attract the wailing wind on cold and stormy nights. The way it, this House always seemed to be doing&#13;
..something.&#13;
He hated the way it looked on the outside with its drab, grey walls and he loathed the way it looked on the inside.&#13;
It was an ugly monstrosity. But his wife had insisted they stay. And so he did what he always did. He muttered under his breath and keep silent and commute to work with minimal complaint and fuss.&#13;
He was beginning to suspect the house hated him too. Because every night at 3:33 A.M. it seemed to find a way to wake him up.&#13;
Sometimes it was as simple as a creaky floor board.&#13;
Other times it was more elaborate.&#13;
The soft thudding of footsteps in the attic right above their bedroom.&#13;
The old grandfather clock in the foyer chiming out thirteen times at random intervals.&#13;
Or the shutters on the windows outside their room slamming shut on a windless night. The eerie sound of tapping and scratching from the old gnarled  tree next to the bedroom window .&#13;
Once, it was the soft laughter of a child, echoing, cackling laughter in all directions.&#13;
And sometimes, it was nothing.&#13;
..Nothing at all.&#13;
He would simply wake up as soon as the clock changed from 3:32 A.M. to 3:33 A.M.&#13;
Their room was at the top of the stairs and from his side of the bed, he could peer down into the darkness below.&#13;
It was so dark at night, the place is pitch black. Sometimes he could only see to the fifth step. But he often got the feeling that something or someone was standing there, just past that fifth step, staring at him from the black with a menacing grin.&#13;
Daring him to walk down the terrifying steps&#13;
He didn’t want to, but he couldn’t help it. Like somebody that drives past a road accident. They just have to see the broken, smashed car. A dark, seductive curiosity.&#13;
He had to look down the foreboding steps, his tired eyes, unadjusted to the dark, always playing tricks on him. He would get up and turn on the light and find the stairs completely empty.&#13;
His wife didn’t believe him of course. He told her the stories. Every morning he seemed to wake with a new one. She told him it was just his imagination.&#13;
She said things like, “stop it with that nonsense and get ready for work, otherwise you’ll be late, Dear”&#13;
By the afternoon, he’d usually managed to convince himself that she was right. It was just his imagination. He’d always had a wild one since he was a child&#13;
But the madness of it all was, he wasn’t imagining anything and his wife was lying to him. She was in on the trick, a part of the gag. For the house had gotten to her first and together they had a hatched a wicked plan.&#13;
It sunk its hooks deep into her soul and she would belong to the house forever, its ever-faithful servant.&#13;
Racing thoughts, suspicion and doubts. Whispering, shouting! In his mind.&#13;
..Shes part of it&#13;
A race against the clock and he had no idea or a clue, he should have started running long ago.&#13;
He was never going to get wise and get out. He was marked for death and thus was doomed.&#13;
He awoke one night, like all the others at 3:33 A.M. It was always 3:33 A.M. The time of night when spirits, friendly or not, are most active. When this old house would come alive.&#13;
Only this time, it was different.&#13;
His wife wasn’t next to him. The space where her warm body had been sound asleep was as empty and cold like ice. .&#13;
And then he heard something,&#13;
..faint whispering&#13;
He heard a moan, low and steady, that seemed to stretch forever and into infinity and beyond.&#13;
It entered through his ears and lodged itself into his head, growing louder, sending a chill, icier than frozen water, down his spine.&#13;
It was accompanied by persistent, rhythmic squeaking, like someone shifting their weight back and forth on a loose floor board over and over and over again.&#13;
The wind picked up outside and howled like a banshee with a megaphone. With a banging on the bedroom window with loud tap!, tapping every few seconds&#13;
And the child from several nights ago chimed in to add its soft, echoing laughter to the orchestra of eerie and foreboding sounds.&#13;
He turned over and stared into the darkness, down to that fifth step and felt his heart freeze in his chest.&#13;
He saw something this time, his heart stopped. Sweating beading on his brow and he held his breath.&#13;
A silhouette clear as day, swaying back in forth — ever so slightly — in rhythm with the creepy house orchestra, was standing just past that fifth step.&#13;
The lights flashed on with an audible crack, for just a split second, then cut out just as quickly. But he’d seen it.&#13;
He’d seen her.&#13;
She has wild tangled, raven black hair which is unkempt and long flowing hair past her shoulders and blowing in an unnatural wind, without wind on the stairs..&#13;
The dark shadows around her crazed eyes are as black as coal. The whites of her eyes were streaked with crimson blood vessels, red snakes swimming in a sea of frozen ice.&#13;
There was no mistaking it. His eyes were not playing tricks on him. He was not imaging anything.&#13;
“Is everything OK?” he called out to his wife.&#13;
All of the noise ceased.&#13;
He could see her lips curling upwards into the wickedest of smiles.&#13;
Deep down, he knew the answer to that question was no. He knew he would not receive a reply. Doom and despair hung in the air so thick you could cut it with a knife, but the man’s mind still tried to convince himself he was dreaming. Last attempt of a sane mind.&#13;
He tried to convince himself that he was fine, that all was well. He hoped that his wife was still&#13;
..  his wife.&#13;
He hoped the devilish and possessed creature of the darkness standing on the steps was someone else.&#13;
.. something else&#13;
He hoped the pure evil that had come for him in the night and now faced him, leering with an insatiable blood lust, was a mistake, an aberration. A trick of the mind&#13;
He hoped that if he closed his eyes tight enough and concentrated hard enough, it would soon be morning and the terrifying scene before him would cease to exist.&#13;
..He really hoped&#13;
</content>
  </story>
  <story>
    <id>1652503096</id>
    <title>My First Love</title>
    <author>Joey Martino</author>
    <date>May/14/2022</date>
    <content>This is a story about the first year of my relationship with the girl I love.&#13;
&#13;
I suppose it starts back in July 2017. She was dating my best friend at the time, they were in a relationship for a few weeks and it ended on bad terms. While they were dating I had only seen her one time, I didn't really say much to her as I am a very shy and socially awkward person. I think I managed to get a few hellos out but nothing more than that.&#13;
&#13;
The next time I met her was on the 31st of October. To be honest I don't really remember that night much since I was black out drunk for the majority of it. By that time things seemed to be ok between her and my friend and that's how I started talking to her more.&#13;
&#13;
In late November we were all talking in group chats, online I am a lot less awkward and am able to talk to other people, so this was a great way for me to start talking to her.&#13;
&#13;
As I started to become more friendly with her I started to realise that she's not how my best friend made her out to be at all.&#13;
We started to hang out more, and the more time I spent with her the closer I felt to her. There are quite a few people in our friends group, I couldn't quite explain why. But I felt like I had some sort of bond with her, like I could connect with her in a way that I couldn't with the other people. Usually I hate it when people hug me, but when she did it always felt warm and comforting.&#13;
&#13;
Where our relationship progressed was on new years eve, I had one of my depressive episodes and ended up leaving all of the group chats I was in. At the time I just felt really lonely, as if I'm destined to never be happy.&#13;
&#13;
She ended up private messaging me, asking what was wrong and why I was feeling like that. There's only a few people that know how much of a shit show my childhood was, I felt comfortable with talking about it with her. And she seemed to have the perfect response to everything. After a while I felt a little better about myself and I will never forget some of the things that she said to me that night.&#13;
&#13;
January..&#13;
We hung out once a week, usually in a group of 7 people. At this point I considered her a very close friend of mine, and without wanting to sound like a white knight SJW. I felt like I wanted to look out for her as much as possible. In that group were a few guys, really creepy. And how they treated her made me feel upset and angry, I wasn't too sure why I felt so strongly towards her. I was convinced that I can't like her due to her being my best friends ex.&#13;
&#13;
Seeing the way these guys were with her lead to me drinking rather heavily, mainly because I felt like there was nothing I could do. Subconsciously I think I knew that I liked her then. And the fact I couldn't say anything or do anything about it really got to me, it started to bring back my depression. I don't usually get angry, and I never used to self harm. But the only thing I could think of doing was punching myself instead. Usually until my hand was really bruised or until my face was bleeding. ( yes I am aware of how retarded I sound right now)&#13;
&#13;
I was In a very bad state mentally. I ended up telling her what was making me feel like that, and she thanked me for it. As it made her feel uncomfortable too.&#13;
&#13;
This is towards the start of February 2018 now. My friend asked me if I like her, to which I replied with, I don't know. I feel as if I can't because you used to date, and if I did it would be a betrayal of our friendship. He was surprisingly good about it and didn't seem to mind. In fact he told me to go for it,&#13;
&#13;
We're in February now and I had decided that I was going to tell her that I liked her. I have never been in a relationship with someone at this point. Never even held another girls hand, let alone kissed one. Saying I was shitting it would be an understatement. I thought to myself how could she ever see me like that, how could she ever want to date an ugly 6'7" fat (in my opinion) autistic, depressed, long haired person with extreme social anxieties.&#13;
&#13;
She is around 5'6". Compared to me she's a genius, slim, and is still the most beautiful girl I've ever seen, every time I talk to her. All of my troubles just seemed to dissappear, and I can just be myself, and happy for a change.&#13;
&#13;
I put quite a lot of thought into how I was going to tell her. I was going to do it the day before valentines. Outside of the pub we usually go to, I wasn't drinking that night as I wanted her to take it seriously.&#13;
&#13;
I had quite a few opportunities to tell her that night. I ended up getting too nervous and I couldn't do it. I really did want to do it in person. But I ended up telling her how I felt online, I don't think she knew how to take it. She said that it was a lot to take in and that she'd need a while to think about it.&#13;
&#13;
It took four really long and nerve wrecking days. But we agreed to meet up by ourselves and talk about it. Something we had never done at that point. That day I was really anxious, having stomach pains. Couldn't stop shaking, I wasn't sure if I should go. I knew that I couldn't do that to her and went, it was quite muddy that day. We met at the train station in the town we usually hang out in. I couldn't start a conversation for shit, thankfully she did most of the talking that day. It was the first time I had ever spent time with another girl by myself (I was 21)&#13;
&#13;
We walked up a hill and sat at the top of it on a bench. It was really muddy that day, she decided that because of how her last relationship ended. She didn't want to rush into anything and she wanted to see how it would go before we decided on starting a relationship. We spent time together every other day. And slowly I became more comfortable with talking to her in person. Within a week I was able to start conversations and cary them on.&#13;
&#13;
I was still really nervous though, and wasn't sure on what was acceptable. To the point where I asked her if it was OK if I held her hand.&#13;
&#13;
On the third of March it was snowing. We met up, and at this point I really wanted to know if she could see up being in a relationship. So I asked her. And she said yes. I will never forget that day. As a first date kind of thing we decided to watch Black Panther. I didn't reallt like it, but i did get salsa on my arse due to the person previously sitting in my seat.&#13;
&#13;
We still wanted to take it slowly, and we did. It took a few weeks for me to be comfortable with kissing her. The first time I kissed her was up on the hill. The one we usually go to to talk about things. That's also something I will never forget, my first kiss.&#13;
&#13;
It's nearly been a year now, and without you I'd still be the introvert kiss - less virgin that I was. And I've loved every single moment of it.&#13;
&#13;
We've been sleeping together in this bed every night for about 6 months now. And while you're in hospital it really does feel empty and lonely without you.&#13;
&#13;
So Kate, if you ever come across this post. I love you, and I can't wait to spend many more years with you.&#13;
&#13;
A lot more happened. But I realise this is getting really really long. So to those of you that read through all of this, well done. And sorry for typos or bad grammar. It's nearly 4am.</content>
  </story>
  <story>
    <id>1652521054</id>
    <title>I cant Believe you are Mine</title>
    <author>Joanna</author>
    <date>May/14/2022</date>
    <content>It was a glorious, colorful autumn.&#13;
&#13;
We’d just left the coffee shop. When we walked by, she had giggled and pulled me inside, saying, “C’mon, let’s be basic white girls and get some pumpkin spice!”&#13;
&#13;
I don’t like coffee. I never had. But when she handed me my cup and looked into my eyes while I tried it, it was the best thing I’d ever tasted.&#13;
&#13;
My hand still tingled where she grabbed it.&#13;
&#13;
As we walked through the park with our drinks, a light drizzle began to fall. She pulled out an umbrella from her bag, I pulled up my hood and hunched my shoulders.&#13;
&#13;
“Don’t be silly,” she giggled, pulling me under the umbrella with her. I couldn’t help but laugh too, her laugh is infectious.&#13;
&#13;
As the sun started to shine again, she pulled me down to sit on a bench. She beamed down at me, and I could only gaze back adoringly.&#13;
&#13;
“So Ava…” She began. I knew this tone of voice, it’s dangerous.&#13;
&#13;
“Who do you like?” She whispered, and I looked away. I wanted to say, ‘you, you, a thousand times you. You’re the only one I can ever think about. You’re gorgeous and sweet and funny and…’&#13;
&#13;
Instead, I shrugged my shoulders and looked down at my cup.&#13;
&#13;
She looked at me with a cautious smile. “If I tell you mine, will you tell me yours?”&#13;
&#13;
“Okay.” I said.&#13;
&#13;
“The person I like… …is you.”&#13;
&#13;
I drop my drink.</content>
  </story>
</stories>
